so we go straight down Center high point
of the head down to the hairline taking
my first section I'm going to go about
an inch and I'll comb it up towards the
ear I cut this so we get our length at
the bottom as opposed to the top and
we're going to work up the head some
more bringing that Guide to the new
section so now we're going to switch to
Vertical in the back here and I'm just
going to Pivot around the head cutting
from short to Long tiny quarter inch
section I don't want a lot of over
Direction horizontally now I'm going to
elevate this up to about here quarter of
an inch guys I don't want to over direct
too much take your time slow and steady
wins the race I'm going to switch to
this opposite side
so now last bit we're across the top of
the head in quarter inch sections ring
section forward
nice little pixie